pridenation.com 2018-04-15

# PrideNation.com | PNN.ONE - PRIVACY POLICY

****

Last Updated on March 30, 2017. This Privacy Policy is effective immediately for users registering for personal accounts after that date and will become effective on March 30, 2017 for pre-existing users.

This Privacy Policy describes our policies on the collection, use, and disclosure of your information in connection with your use of our websites, emails, and mobile applications ("Site"). The terms "we", "us", "PNN ONE" and "Pridenation" refer to PNN a product of PNN Media Group out of Palm Springs, CA. When you use the Site, you consent to our collection, use, and disclosure of your information as described in this Privacy Policy.  

INFORMATION YOU SUBMIT

We may store the information you submit to or through the Site. We use the information to fulfill your requests, provide Site functionality, improve Site quality, personalize the user experience, display relevant advertising, provide customer support, message you, back up our systems, allow for disaster recovery, and comply with legal obligations. Among the information you submit to or through the Site, please note:

Account Registration: You must provide a valid email address in order to sign up for an Account on the Site. In addition, you may provide us with your full name, gender, and birth date. When you sign up for a PNN account, we opt you in to receive emails from other PNN users, business owners and PNN by default. You can manage your email preferences and modify some of the information associated with your account here. Note that you cannot opt out of receiving required administrative or legal notices. If you feel that an unauthorized account has been created depicting you or your likeness, you can request its removal here.

Public Content: Your reviews, tips, photos, check-ins, check-in comments, likes, message board posts, bookmarks, friends, lists, compliments, account profile (including your gender, first name and last initial, but excluding your other account registration information), and other content you post to the Site are meant for public consumption. We may display this content on the Site, and further distribute it to a wider audience through third party sites and services.  
Contacts: You can invite your friends to join the Site by providing their contact information, or by allowing us to use your address book from your computer, mobile device, or other sites. If you invite a friend to join and connect with you on the Site, we may use and store your friends' contact information long enough to process your requests.

Messaging: If you exchange messages with others through the Site, we may store these messages in order to deliver them and allow you to manage them. If you send information from the Site to your phone via SMS text message, we may log your phone number, phone carrier, and the date and time that the message was processed. Carriers may charge recipients for texts that they receive.

Credit Card Purchases: If you purchase PNN products or services, such as PNN Deals and PNN Gift Certificates, we may collect and store billing and credit card information. This information will only be shared with third parties who perform tasks required to complete the purchase transaction (such as fulfilling orders and processing credit card payments). When you submit credit card numbers, we encrypt that information using industry standard technology.  
For more information on controlling your personal data, please see Sections 4 and 5, below.

COOKIES AND OTHER INFORMATION WE COLLECT

In addition to the information you submit to or through the Site, we also collect and store information from and about you in the course of your use of the Site. We use this information to analyze and track user behavior, personalize your experience, associate it with other information about you, provide the functionality and improve the quality of the Site, help comply with legal obligations, and may use it to display relevant advertising. We collect this information in a couple of different ways:

Cookies: We may use cookies, web beacons, local shared objects (sometimes called "flash cookies"), and similar technology in connection with your use of the Site ("Cookies"). Cookies are small data files that may have unique identifiers, and reside, among other places, on your computer or mobile device, in emails we send to you, and on our web pages. Cookies may transmit information about you and your use of the Site, such as your browser type, search preferences, data relating to advertisements that have been displayed to you or that you have clicked on, and the date and time of your use. You can disable some (but not all) Cookies in your device or browser settings, but doing so may affect your ability to use the Site. To learn how to manage privacy and storage settings for local shared objects in particular, [click here](http://pnn.email/).

Server Logs: Our servers log information about your use of the Site, such as your search activity, the pages you view, the date and time of your visit, and the businesses you call using our mobile applications. Our servers also log information that your computer or mobile device provides to us in connection with your use of the Site, such as your browser type, browser language, IP address, mobile carrier, unique device identifier, location, and requested and referring URLs. You may be able to adjust the settings on your computer or mobile device to limit the information it shares with us here.

THIRD PARTIES

We do not rent, share, sell or trade personally identifiable information with third parties for their direct marketing purposes. That said, please note the following:

Advertising and Third Party Cookies: We allow third parties who provide services relating to advertising to use Cookies, as defined above, in connection with your use of the Site. As a result, they may collect and store the same type of information and use it for the same type of purposes as described for PNN above, and they may be able to associate the information they collect with other information they have about you from other sources. We do not necessarily have access to or control over the Cookies they use. Nevertheless, you may be able to opt-out of some of their practices by visiting the following links: Network Advertising Initiative, Omniture, Aperture, and PrivacyChoice. Please note that opting out does not prevent you from receiving advertisements.

Service Providers: Some of the services that are offered through the Site are provided by third party providers, like dinner reservations, food delivery, and the like. We also outsource some of our own functions to third party providers, such as technical and customer support, tracking and reporting functions, quality assurance testing, payment processing functions, and other services. We may share information from or about you with these third party providers so that they can perform their services or complete your requests.

Aggregate Information: We may share user information in the aggregate with third parties, such as advertisers and content distributors. For example, we may disclose the number of users that have been exposed to, or clicked on, advertisements.

Business Transfers: We may share information from or about you with subsidiaries, joint ventures, or other companies under common control, in which case we will require them to honor this Privacy Policy. If another company acquires PNN or all or substantially all of our assets, that company will possess the same information, and will assume the rights and obligations with respect to that information as described in this Privacy Policy.

Investigations: We may investigate and disclose information from or about you if we have a good faith belief that such investigation or disclosure is (a) reasonably necessary to comply with legal process and law enforcement instructions and orders, such as a search warrant, subpoena, statute, judicial proceeding, or other legal process served on us; (b) helpful to prevent, investigate, or identify possible wrongdoing in connection with the Site; or (c) protect our rights, reputation, property, or that of our users affiliates, or the public.

Links: The Site may contain links to unaffiliated third party websites. Except as set forth herein, we do not share your personal information with them, and are not responsible for their privacy practices. We suggest you read the privacy policies on all such third party websites.

Facebook and Twitter: If you are logged into Facebook, and you access but are not logged into the Site, we may receive information from Facebook to make it easier for you to create an account on the Site and show you relevant content from your Facebook friends. This information personalizes your experience and helps you create a PNN account. To learn more about this feature and how to block aspects of it, please click here and here. You can also connect your PNN account to your accounts on third party services like Facebook or Twitter, in which case we may collect and store information identifying your account with the third party service. We use the information to help you connect and share public content with your friends and followers. You can manage these settings here.

CONTROLLING YOUR PERSONAL DATA

Other users may be able to identify you, or associate you with your user account if you include personal information in your Public Content. You can reduce the risk of being personally identified by using the Site pseudonymously, though doing so could detract from the credibility of your contributions to the Site. Users can also use the Member Search feature to find one another based on their names or email addresses. You can opt-out of this feature here.

Please also note that the messages you send or receive using the Site are only private to the extent that you and the sender/recipient keep them private. For example, we do not have any control over whether a recipient of one of your personal messages publicly posts it or its contents.

DATA RETENTION AND ACCOUNT TERMINATION

When logged into your account, you can remove or edit a review that you have posted to the Site by clicking on the respective links below the review. You can also terminate your personal account by clicking here. If you terminate your account, we may continue to show some of your content in anonymized form. We may also keep personal information in our active systems for a period of 5 years (or longer if required by law) in order to ensure our ability to satisfy the authorized uses under this Privacy Policy. For example, we may use retained data to prevent, investigate, or identify possible wrongdoing in connection with the Site or to comply with legal obligations. Please also note that information may exist in backup storage even after it has been removed from our active databases. If you are terminating a business account, the personal information associated with your account will be removed according to the terms of this Policy. However your business listing will remain visible, including consumer reviews about your business.

We will respond to requests relating to personal data sent from within the European Union according to the procedures mandated by the member state from where the request is sent. You will receive a response to your request within 30 days.

CHILDREN

The Site is intended for general audiences and is not directed to children under 18. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 18. If you become aware that a child has provided us with personal information without parental consent, please contact us here. If we become aware that a child under 18 has provided us with personal information without parental consent, we take steps to remove such information and terminate the child's account.

SECURITY

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet or via mobile device, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

DISPUTE RESOLUTION

If you believe that PNN has not adhered to this Privacy Policy you may write to the PNN Privacy Officer at the following page link:

MODIFICATIONS TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

We may revise this Privacy Policy from time to time. The most current version of the Privacy Policy will govern our use of your information and will be located here. If we make material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you by email or by posting a notice on the Site prior to the effective date of the changes. By continuing to access or use the Site after those changes become effective, you agree to be bound by the revised Privacy Policy.
